Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
5583/1
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
120 linear ft.
Records (documents), publications (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Publications, manuals, policies, and plans issued by a large sample of Fortune 500 corporations and by a variety of organizations, such as professional and trade associations, government agencies, and educational and cultural organizations. The materials issued by corporations include company histories, employee newsletters, employee benefit plans, personnel practice manuals, performance appraisal forms, affirmative action policies, training brochures, job descriptions, and career development programs as well as national trade association documents and recruitment material.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Several economic activities(sectors) are represented in the collection, such as manufacturing, transportation, mining, banking, insurance, utilities, trade, and services. Corporations whose pamphlets are held in the collection include AT&T, Bethlehem Steel, Bell Telephone System, Firestone Tire & Rubber, Ford Motor Co., General Electric, General Foods, General Mills, General Motors, Goodyear Tire & Rubber, Heinz, International Harvester, Johnson & Johnson, Lockheed Aircraft Co., Maytag Co., Metropolitan Life Insurance Co., National Association of Manufacturers, Pennsylvania Railroad Co., Radio Corporation of America (RCA), Standard Oil, Tennessee Valley Authority, Union Carbide, and Westinghouse Electric among numerous other corporations.
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into six sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Section 5: Boxes 89-110
Section 6: Boxes 111-121
SUBJECTS
Names:
A. Philip Randolph Institute.; Abbott Laboratories.; Abbott Laboratories. House Organs.; Abraham & Straus.; Addressograph-Multigraph Corporation.; Administrative Management Society.; Adult Education Association.; Aero Supply Mfg. Co.; Aerojet-General Corporation.; Aeroquip Corporation.; Aerospace Industries Association of America.; Aetna Life Insurance Company (Hartford, Conn.); Affiliated Schools for Workers.; African- American Labor Center.; Agway Inc.; Air Reduction Company.; Air Transport Association of America.; Airlines Negotiating Committee.; Alaska. Department of Administration.Division of Personnel.; Alden's, Inc.; Alexander Smith & Sons, Carpet Co.; Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corporation.; Allegheny Metal.; Allied Chemical & Dye Corporation; Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company.; Aluminum Company of America.; American Arbitration Association.; American Brake Shoe Company.; American Can Company.; American Labor Education Service.; American Locomotive Company.; American Management Association.; American Merchant Marine Institute.; American Metal Climax, Inc.; American Motors Corporation.; American Petroleum Institute.; American Plan Association.; American Society of Safety Engineers.; American Telephone and Telegraph Company.; American Textile Manufacturers Institute.; American Thread Company.; American Trucking Associations.; American Type Founders Company.; American Vocational Association.; Americans Against Union Control of Government.; Amtrak.; Anaconda American Brass Company.; Anaconda Company.; Anaconda Copper Mining Company.; Anaconda Wire and Cable Company.; Anchor Hocking Glass Corporation.; Armco Steel Corporation.; Armour and Company.; Armstrong Cork Company.; Associated Builders & Contractors (U.S.); Associated General Contractors of America.; Association of American Railroads.; Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railroad Company.; Atlantic Refining Company.; Atlas Chemical Industries.; ATO, Inc.; Automobile Manufacturers Association.; Automotive and Aviation Parts Manufacturers.; Automotive Council for War Production.; Bell & Howell Co.; Bell Aircraft Corporation.; Bell of Pennsylvania.; Bell Telephone Company.; Bell Telephone Laboratories.; Bethlehem Steel Corporation.; Bird and Son, Inc.; Bituminous Coal Operators' Association.; Bloomer Brothers.; Boeing Aerospace Company.; Boeing Company.; Borden Company.; Brockway Glass Company.; Building Trades Employers' Association.; Bureau of National Affairs (Arlington, Va.); Burlington Industries, Inc.; Burndy Engineering Company.; Burrough Corporation.; California Institute of Technology. Industrial Relations Center.; California Institute of Technology.; California State Personnel Board.; Canadian National Railways; Canadian Pacific Railway Company.; Carborundum Company (Niagara Falls, N.Y.); Carnation Company.; Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation.; Carrier Corporation.; Caterpillar Tractor Company.; Celanese Corporation.; Central Hudson Gas and Electric Corporation.; Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America.; Chemical Corn Exchange Bank.; Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company.; Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of Maryland.; Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of Virginia.; Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company.; Chessie System, inc.; Chicago Transit Authority.; Chrysler Corporation.; Cincinnati Bell Inc.; Civil Service Assembly of the United States and Canada.; Climax Molybdenum Company.; Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A.; Colgate-Palmolive Company.; Colorado Fuel and Iron Company.; Columbia Gas Company.; Commerce and Industry Association of New York.; Committee for the Nation's Health.; Commonwealth Edison Company.; Communications Workers of America.; Cone Mills Corporation.; Connecticut General Life Insurance Company.; Consolidated Edison Company of New York, inc.; Consolidated Gas, Electric Light, and Power Company of Baltimore.; Consolidated Natural Gas Company.; Consolidated Vultee Aircraft Corporation.; Consumers' League of New York City.; Consumers Power Company (Mich.); Container Corporation of America.; Continental Can Company.; Continental Insurance Company.; Continental Oil Company.; Cooperative League of the U.S.A.; Corn Products Refining Company.; Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory.; Cornell University.; Corning Glass Works.; Council Against Communist Aggression (U.S.); Council for International Progress in Management (USA); Council of Profit Sharing Industries (U.S.); Crane Co.; Crane Packing Co.; Credit Union National Association.; Crouse-Hinds Company.; Crown Zellerbach Corporation.; Crucible Steel Company of America.; Dan River Mills Inc.; Dartnell Corporation.; Daystrom, inc.; Dartnell Corporation.; Deere & Company.; Detroit Edison Company.; Diamond Alkali Company.; Dictaphone Corp.; Dole Food Company.; Douglas Aircraft Company.; Dow Chemical Company.; E.I. du Pont de Nemours & Company.; Eagle Pencil Company.; Eastern Gas and Fuel Associates.; Eastern Western & Southwestern Canier Company.; Eastman Kodak Company.; Eaton Corporation.; Eaton Manufacturing Company.; Ecusta Paper Company.; Electronic Industries Alliance.; Eli Lilly and Company.; Employers' Association of Chicago.; Employers' Association of Detroit.; Employers' Association of Grand Rapids.; Employers' Association of Massachusetts.; Employers' Association of Milwaukee.; Employers' Association of Pittsburgh.; Employers' Association of Washington.; Employers' Group of Insurance Companies.; Employers' Labor Relations Information Committee.; Employers' of Mutual of Wasau.; Engineers Joint Council. Engineering Manpower Commission.; Erie Railroad Company.; Erie-Lackawanna Railroad Company.; Erlanger Mills, Inc.; Erwin Cotton Mills.; Esso Research and Engineering Company.; Esso Standard Oil Company.; Exxon Corporation; Falstaff Brewing Corporation; Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America; Federal Professional Association (U.S.); Federal Reserve Bank of New York; Federated Employers of San Francisco; Federated Employers of the Bay Area; Fieldcrest Mills Inc.; William Filene's Sons Co.; Firestone Tire and Rubber Company; First National Bank (Ithaca, N.Y.); First National Bank Maryland; First National Bank of Boston; First National Bank of Chicago; First National Bank of Portland (Portland, Me.); First National Bank of St. Louis; First Pennsylvania Bank, N.A.; First Pennsylvania Banking and Trust Company, Philadelphia.; Fischer and Porter Company; Florida Power & Light Company; Ford Foundation; Ford Motor Company; Foster and Forbes Glass Company; Foundation for Economic Education, inc.; General Dynamics Corporation.; General Electric Company; George Fischer, Ltd.; J.N. Adam & Company.; New Jersey Bell Telephone Company.; New York Chamber of Commerce.; Society for Equitable Assurances on Lives and Survivorships.; South Central Bell.; University of California, Berkeley. Institute of Industrial Relations.; William Filene's Sons Co.; Commonwealth Edison Company; A. Philip Randolph Institute; ATO, Inc.; Aero Supply Mfg. Co.; Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
Subjects:
Adult education; Aeronautics; Agricultural industries; Aluminum industry and trade; Airlines; Aircraft industry; Agricultural machinery; Architectural metal-work; Audio equipment industry; Automobile industry and trade; Arbitration, Industrial; Agricultural chemicals industry; Audio equipment industry; Bituminous materials industry; Building trades; Buildings--Environmental engineering; Banks and banking; Breweries; Baked products industry; Business consultants; Clothing trade; Coal mines and mining; Chemical industry; Compressor industry; Clerks (Retail trade); Computer industry; Cereal products; Consumer protection; Container industry; Credit unions; Clay industries; Cement industries; Copper alloys; Dairy products industry; Detergent industry; Executives--Training of; Electric power transmission; Electronics industries; Food industry and trade; Frozen foods and industry; Footwear industry; Fruit trade; Farm produce--Marketing--Government policy; Finance, Public; Glass container industry; Glass manufacture; Gas extraction; Grain trade; Grocery trade; Gasket industry; Human capital; Hydroelectric power plants; Life insurance.; Iron industry and trade; Property insurance.; Casualty insurance.; Instructional materials industry; Health insurance.; Investment banking; Infant formula industry; Knit good industry; Labor unions; Local transit; Luggage industry; Logging; Medical supplies industry; Medicaid; Motor vehicle industry; Metal trade; Meat industry and trade; Military vehicle industry; Medical instruments and apparatus industry; Management; Measuring instruments; Natural gas pipelines; Notions (Merchandise); Newspaper publishing; Navigation equipment industry; National security; Office management; Office equipment and supplies; Petroleum refineries; Photographic industry; Paper folding (Graphic design); Public utilities; Paper products industry; Political participation; Plastics industry and trade; Pharmaceutical industry; Paint industry and trade; Public administration; Public opinion polls; Paper bag industry; Retail trade; Rug and carpet industry; Railroads; Rubber industry and trade; Railroad equipment industry; Roller bearings; Security systems industry; Service industries; Social security; Shipment of goods; Sanitary supply industry; Soybean industry; Slaughtering and slaughter-houses; Transportation equipment industry.; Telecommunication.; Trucking industry.; Trucks--Design and construction.; Textile industry.; Trade associations.; Tobacco industry.; Universities and colleges.; Vocational education.; Wood products.; Welding equipment industry.; Woolen goods industry.
Form and Genre Terms:
Records (documents); Publications (documents)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this Collection:
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AFF) Part 1
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AFF) Part 1, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AFF) Part 1, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AFF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66 5583/1: Archives Organization File (AFF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AFF) Part 1, Section 5: Boxes 89-110
Related Collections:
5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents
5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3
5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6
5956: Archives Organization File Additional records
CONTAINER LIST
- Box: 111, Folder: 1 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Personnel Manual, Publication (Box 111, Folder 1)
    Item is in English.
- Box: 111, Folder: 2 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Safety Digest Vol. 11, No. 5, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
    May 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Description of the Permanent Total Disability Plan, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
    1951 Edition. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Texaco Topics: 7th War Loan Vol. 14, No. 5, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
    June, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Texaco Correspondence, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Survey of Occupations for Handicapped Veterans, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Manual for Counsellors to Employes Returning from Military Service, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Policy Covering Leaves of Absence for Employees of the Texas Company and Its Domestic Subsidiaries Returning from Military Leave and Eligible to Benefits under the G.I. Bill, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: The Supervisor and Human Relations, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Employees Progress Report, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Program for Development and Understanding of Industrial Relations Policies in the Texas Company, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Manual for Counsellors to Employes Returning from Military Services, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: The Texas Company: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: The Foreman as a Manager, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Checklist for Company Materials, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: A Guide for Establishing a Program of Supervisory Training, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: The Texaco Star, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
    Midwinter 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Texaco Star, Publication (Box 111, Folder 2)
    Spring 1945. Item is in English.
- Box: 111, Folder: 3 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Description of the Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Health Division Services, Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: You and Your Company, Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Employe Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Employe Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Texaco, Inc. Pre-Interview Information, Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Texaco Pre-Interview Information, Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: A Short History of Texaco, Inc., Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
    1902-1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Protecting the Environment: We are all custodians of our planet, Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Opportunities with Texaco, Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: The Texaco Star, Number 1, Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Opportunities with Texaco, Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Texaco Topics: A Special 1977 Issue Commemerating Texaco's 75th Anniversary, Publication (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Box: 111, Folder: 4 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Texaco Research Center: Beacon, NY, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Texaco's Heritage and The Way Ahead with Introductory Remarks, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
    By W.S.S. Rodgers, Harry T. Klein and J.S. Leach. April 7, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Texaco: Careers in Research, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Opportunities with Texaco, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Opportunities with Texaco, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Texaco Tuition Aid Plan, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Employes Savings Plan, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Group Pension Plan and Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Educational Loan Program for Employes' Plan, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Hospital Surgical Major Medical Benefits Plan, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Accident and Sick Benefit Plan, Permanent Total Disability Plan, The Vacation Plan, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Careers in Research, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Opportunities with Texaco, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Not Entirely a Man's World, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Texaco Merit Scholarship Program, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Employe Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Employe Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Descirption of the Permanent Total Disability Plan, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Description of the Hospital and Surgical Benefits Plan for Employes`1951 Edition, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Description of the Group Life Insurance and Pension Plan, Publication (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Box: 111, Folder: 5 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Texaco Topics, Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    November-December 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Texaco People, Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    October 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Texaco Topics, Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The Texaco Star, Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    Fall 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Texaco Star, Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: The Texaco Star, Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Texas Topics No. 4, Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: 40th Anniversary, Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
    1902-1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: You and Your Company, Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: The Vacation Plan, The Accident and Sick Benefit Plan, The Permanent Total Disability Plan, Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Report to Texaco Employes on How We Made Out in 1949, Publication (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Box: 111, Folder: 6 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report of The Texas Company's Conference on Foremanship, Publication (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Box: 111, Folder: 7 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Membership Information, Publication (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Security/Safety Notice, Publication (Box 111, Folder 7)
    May, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Some Examples of Insurance Premiums per Pay Day, Publication (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Summary Plan Description of: The TI Severance Pay Plan, Publication (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Security/Safety Notice: New Employee Edition, Publication (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Supplement to Summary Plan Descriptions of Certain Welfare Plans for Employees of Texas Instruments Incorporated (TI) and Certain Participating Subsidiary Companies, Publication (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Texas Instruments: At TI, you start out ahead the day you start work, Publication (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Activities and Facilities: 25th Anniversary, Publication (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Box: 111, Folder: 8 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Working Rules for Employes of the Texas Pipe Line Company (North Texas Division), Publication (Box 111, Folder 8)
- Box: 111, Folder: 9 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Retiree Comprehensive Medical Plan, Publication (Box 111, Folder 9)
    Revised July 1, 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Disability Income Insurance, Publication (Box 111, Folder 9)
    Revised July 1, 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Life Insurance, Publication (Box 111, Folder 9)
    Printed June 1, 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Basic Health, Major Medical and Dental, Publication (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: 24-Hour Accident Insurance, Publication (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: The Thatcher Glass Story, Publication (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Procedure: Discharge Notice, Publication (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Thatcher Glass Manufacturing Company, Inc. Lettter to Employees, Publication (Box 111, Folder 9)
    February 24, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Thatcher Glass Salaried Personnel Appraisal (Exempt), Publication (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Employees' Handbook: Thatcher Glass, Publication (Box 111, Folder 9)
- Box: 111, Folder: 10 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: We'll be 50 Years Old Tomorrow, Publication (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: A Primer for Postwar Prosperity, Publication (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Thompson Products: A Decade of Achievement, Publication (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Pension Plan for Eligible Employees of Thompson Products, Inc. Cleveland Plants, Publication (Box 111, Folder 10)
    August 15, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: To Members of the Thompson Organization, Publication (Box 111, Folder 10)
    March 5, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Stopping grievances before they grow, Publication (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Organization of Personnel Administration and Labor Relations Policies of Thompson Products, Inc. Cleveland, Ohio, Publication (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: We Led With Our Chin: A Report on a Survey of Employee Opinion Conducted in Cleveland Plants of Thompson Products, Inc. and Thompson Aircraft Products Co., Publication (Box 111, Folder 10)
    August 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: We Led With Our Chin: A Report on a Survey of Employee Opinion Conducted in Cleveland Plants of Thompson Products, Inc. and Thompson Aircraft Products Co., Publication (Box 111, Folder 10)
    August, 1944. Item is in English.
- Box: 111, Folder: 11 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin: EDP and Personnel, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
    By Richard T. Bueschel. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Corigan, Eliz Alpha-Locator Card, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Personnel Requisition, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Personnel Requisition: Key Punch Edit Sheet, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Personnel Requisition, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Personnel Requisition, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Week Ending Sep 18 1966, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Employee Record: Department Copy, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Merit Raise Recommendation, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Personnel Profile, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: Employee Status and Change Record, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: Employee Record: Personnel Copy, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Notification of Management/Specialist Vacancy, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: Open Requisition List as of 9/28/66, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
    Seotember 28, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Exhibit I Diagram, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Item 17: Monday, October 3rd, 1966 Schedule, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)
    October 3rd, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: An Introduction to Dartmouth College, Publication (Box 111, Folder 11)